Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
THE ISLAND OF LAMPEDUSA
MEDITERRANEAN SEA
In the first batch.
we've got 20 refugees.
All young girls.
Feel free to keep one.
I'm afraid you've got the wrong address.
But the merchandise is excellent.
A real bargain.
Some of them are barely 12.
It's a lot of money.
All you need to do
is to help us get them here.
My family has never been
into this sort of business.
I don't have to do anything.
You're only wasting my time.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to offend you.
Think it over.
You'll get a good cut.
Mario.
Fucking assholes.
However.
he's a potential business partner.
He deserves our respect.
Even if he is an asshole.
What were you looking at?
Oh. my son. You have to be careful.
Beautiful women are heaven for the eyes
- and hell for the soul.
- And purgatory for the wallet.
Listen to me.
It's time for you to stop thinking about
fun and pleasure.
You have to take on
your responsibilities. okay?
One day. all of this... will be yours.
♪ You keep telling me I'm free to go ♪
♪ But I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ It's a lie. it's a lie. it's a lie ♪
♪ When I'm not here. you're alone ♪
♪ And you walk by your own ♪
♪ Don't you lie. won't you lie
Don't you lie ♪
♪ And I think you should know ♪
♪ That I won't let it go ♪
♪ It was like a million times ♪
365 DAYS
♪ I'm singing a lullaby ♪
♪ And I think you should know ♪
♪ That I won't let it go ♪
♪ I thought that it was enough ♪
5 YEARS LATER
♪ But I don't want to say goodbye... ♪
We are terribly sorry.
but it was possible to regain
only 12 percent of your family's assets.
In the future. we recommend
a more heterogeneous investment portfolio.
You recommend?
This investment
was also highly recommended by you.
- Good evening.
WARSAW
Have you packed your shit already?
Please. could anyone tell me
what the hell happened here yesterday?
I expect a refund
and five percent interest.
It's impossible.
- Refund. and ten percent interest.
Until the end of the month.
My question is:
How the fuck...
did it happen?
Hmm?
You should ask Ms. Biel.
Excuse my language.
but you need to have balls to do this job.
This conversation is over.
- This is America.
Ms. Biel?
- First of all. it's not my fault.
- Listen. ma'am...
I haven't finished yet.
And it's not my job
to temper rowdy customers.
And I think you should rather tell us
why. in the entire building.
there were only two security guards.
Word... It is all about word
that you've given to my family.
What is it?
You have this game in America. right?
Trick or treat.
I checked in the band
at our hotel on purpose.
And because of yesterday's incident.
we are in media from the US to Japan.
I thought that when it comes
to sexual preferences.
nothing would surprise me.
but you...
What would your loving husband say
about that?
Your kids? Shareholders?
Shall I continue?
You've embarrassed us
in the eyes of entire world.
We all know how the media
and the stock market will react
when I make it all public.
There have been so many reservations
that we are overbooked
for the next four weekends.
After a week...
bank shares will fall by half.
It was possible because of my strategy.
Age and sex had nothing to do with it.
After a month. I will buy it for peanuts.
only to...
This is exactly
what you need balls for.
...fire you all.
In my office. Right away.
What are you gonna do about my money?
♪ Every time you wanna walk out the door ♪
♪ I don't blame you ♪
♪ And I think you should know ♪
♪ That I won't let it go ♪
♪ It was like a million times ♪
♪ I'm singing a lullaby ♪
♪ And I think you should know ♪
♪ That I won't let you go ♪
♪ I thought that it was enough ♪
♪ But I don't want to say goodbye ♪
♪ And I think you should know ♪
- - ♪ And it's hard for me ♪
♪ Hard for me. hard for me ♪
♪ And it's hard for me. hard for me ♪
♪ Hard for me ♪
♪ Yeah. it's hard for me ♪
Hi. honey.
Damn. I have to finish this.
Give me like half an hour. okay?
Can't you just take a small break?
Yeah. sure.
You must be tired.
We have a plane to catch in the morning.
You shouldn't strain yourself
with that weak heart of yours.
Hmm?
Besides. you probably haven't packed
for us yet. right?
I'm going to kill them.
What's the matter?
Somebody has taken our container
with the cocaine.
♪ Rings and rosies ♪
♪ Everybody's falling down ♪
♪ I've got your posies ♪
♪ Stuff your pockets. turn around ♪
♪ Ashes. ashes ♪
♪ We all go home ♪
♪ I am the fire burning ♪
♪ I rise with the flames ♪
♪ I am the fire ♪
♪ Take me to the fire burning ♪
♪ I rise with the flames ♪
♪ I am the fire burning ♪
♪ Take me to the fire burning ♪
♪ I rise with the flames ♪
♪ I am the fire burning ♪
♪ I am the fire ♪
♪ I am the fire. I am the fire ♪
♪ Ashes. ashes ♪
- ♪ Ashes. ashes ♪
- ♪ We all go home ♪
- ♪ Ashes. ashes ♪
- ♪ Ashes. ashes ♪
- ♪ We all go home ♪
Let's drink to the health
of the sexiest. the best.
and most wonderful woman in the world...
my mother.
I was just kidding! I'm sorry.
I meant my lovely Laura.
who will. in a second. turn... 29.
Come on. you make me feel old.
Old. but still kicking.
One moment.
Today is the birthday...
of my beautiful girlfriend. Laura.
Ah...
Please. give me a hand.
What are you up to?
Yes?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Whoo!
Yes. thank you.
♪ Happy birthday. Laura ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Bravo!
Cheers.
Jesus. Martin. you are such a dumbass.
- My favorite. You remembered.
- Aww.
- But...
- What?
To be honest... I didn't order it.
Maybe it's on the house?
All right.
so we probably should drink to...
No. Wait. I have to go to the bathroom.
Can't fight Maslow's pyramid.
Are you lost. baby girl?
- It was just like him.
- Yeah.
Look! Our wine is here.
That's what I'm talking about.
Grazie.
Okay. thank you.
God. why do these seagulls
have to be so loud?
Where is Michał- angelo?
As you can see.
the child is playing in the wading pool.
What about Martin?
I don't know.
He wasn't there when I woke up.
I don't know where he is.
He doesn't answer his phone.
What? But it's your birthday.
You don't say.
The next one is just a year away.
You know what?
I'm not the most important thing to him.
In Martin's hierarchy.
I'm way behind his buddies and his work.
And most importantly. way behind him.
Hi. honey.
How are you? How about lunch?
Lunch? Sure. Where were you?
Etna. You were sleeping like a log.
Didn't want to wake you. Time's a-wasting.
Yeah. time's a-wasting. Did you have fun?
Jesus. It was fucking awesome.
You would have liked it.
You can experience the sea and snow
at the same time. Cool!
Idiot! Don't you remember?
We were supposed to go there together!
Why have you left me all alone
on my birthday?
Jesus. Don't get so worked up.
With your weak heart.
you shouldn't do that.
Fuck off with that heart argument again.
Do you care about
anything other than yourself?
- What am I to you?
- You think I don't care about you?
I've been looking for this
for over an hour.
Huh?
See? It's for you.
Hmm?
Mmm. Thank you very much.
- Now. fuck off!
♪ They come with bows and arrows ♪
♪ They come with their swords drawn ♪
♪ They come with pistols at their sides ♪
♪ And torches lit with fire ♪
♪ They're stormin' every castle ♪
♪ Hoping to steal our gold ♪
♪ Envious of the way
We have what they can never hold ♪
♪ We are the hunted ♪
♪ We are the chosen ones ♪
♪ We are the wanted ♪
♪ We are what they can't touch ♪
Good evening.
Fuck me.
Are you lost. baby girl?
You...
Suck it.
You had a bad reaction to the sedative.
I didn't know you have a heart problem.
Suck it yourself.
Why am I here? Who the fuck you are?
And why are you keeping me here?
Answer me.
- Sit. I don't want you to faint again.
- Answer me.
- Sit down.
- I'm not your property!
Sit the fuck down.
Do you wanna know why you are here.
or not?
Thank you.
I think you should have a drink.
What I am about to tell you
is so incredible that I...
I wouldn't have believed it's true
until I saw you at the airport.
In that moment. I understood that...
it wasn't only my imagination.
Five years ago.
my whole life was changed.
My father died...
in front of my eyes.
The bullet went through his heart...
and hit me.
I thought I would die too.
When my heart stop. I saw you.
Every day. I had this image
in front of my eyes.
I was looking for you around the world.
Somewhere inside me.
I had this feeling of certainty that...
one day you would stand in front of me
and be mine.
You must be kidding.
Nobody owns me. I'm not an object.
You can't have me just like that;
kidnap me and think that I'm all yours.
I know.
But that's why I'm giving you
a chance to fall in love with me.
Not because I made you do it.
because you will want to.
But I've got a boyfriend
who is going to look for me.
I've got family. friends...
I've got my own life.
I don't need a chance for love from you!
So. I kindly ask you
to let me the fuck out!
Your boyfriend doesn't deserve you.
My people have taken your stuff
from the room...
and left a note for Martin.
It says that...
you're coming back to Poland.
moving out...
disappearing from his life.
You know what?
Fuck off.
I won't do anything
without your permission.
I'll wait until you want me.
you desire me.
and come to me yourself.
I won't tie you up.
but don't provoke me.
I can't be gentle.
I'm not used to tolerating disobedience.
You have 365 days.
I'd do anything
so you can fall in love with me.
If next year. on your birthday.
nothing change. I'll set you free.
Okay.
Now. you put down the gun...
or this will be stop being funny.
Do you really wanna kill me?
Many have tried. It's not that easy.
Excuse me.
There's been a delivery.
You need to sign.
Take her to her room.
Okay. let's go.
Massimo.
There will be problems.
The conflict with the Gattuso family
might ruin the business.
Mind your own business.
I'm doing it. It is my duty
to protect the family and you.
Even from yourself.
Shoot me.
Get everyone here.
Here comes Massimo the Great.
What are you going to do to me? Beat me?
Cut off my balls?
If you'd only stolen from me.
you'd be off the hook now.
But you decided to sell children
to a brothel.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
- We all have skeletons in the closet...
- Shut up.
You have smeared
the name of this family. Alfredo.
What family?
What values?
Spare me this bullshit. and shoot me.
You will be erased.
No trace will be left of you...
as if you never existed.
That's your punishment.
You see those marks?
- Unbelievable.
- The scumbag.
Fuck.
How are you feeling?
You shouldn't have seen it.
But you have to know that he deserved it.
He had been hurting children.
Cheating and stealing on his family.
We don't forgive it.
He killed himself
with what he'd been doing.
It wasn't me who changed your clothes.
It was the maid.
You have people for everything.
It's... It's one of the advantages
of being a boss.
So. tell one of your butlers
to bring my cell phone and laptop.
I can see you've got your strength back.
You will have your cell phone
and your laptop
when it's the right time.
Now...
if you need anything.
Domenico is here to help you.
Be ready in two hours.
because we need to buy some stuff
before we depart.
Depart? Where to?
What are you talking about?
I'm not flying anywhere.
unless it's Poland.
It wasn't an offer;
- it was an order.
- Listen to me.
I'm not a bag of potatoes
that you can transfer
without my permission.
If that's your idea of
how falling in love with you looks.
you're fucking wrong.
If you hit me again...
What? You will kill me?
This is what you call a temper?
How come you're not Italian?
How many Polish girls do you know?
It looks like one is all I need to know.
It will be a good year.
I just need to react quicker.
'cause I lose my vigilance
when I'm around you.
Domenico brought all of your stuff.
Impressive amount of shoes
for a five-day holiday.
♪ The radio
The radio's about to explode ♪
♪ Oh. baby
Don't waste your time or our lives ♪
♪ The radio
The radio's about to explode ♪
♪ I have to have my dose now
Or I'll die ♪
Breakfast is ready. miss.
I'll do my best to help you.
I think your boss wants me to gain weight.
I think he just wants
to take good care of you. you know?
But I think you're here to help me
with everything what I need.
So. I need you to sit down...
and help me to eat.
Okay.
♪ Love me. love me
Love me now ♪
♪ Touch me. touch me
Touch me now ♪
♪ Let me check inside you ♪
Today. I have some business
to take care of.
You will accompany me.
I said. I'm not going anywhere.
♪ Baby. my mind is on ready now ♪
♪ Lady. tell me something
'Cause I need somebody... ♪
Etna.
Known also as "Mongibello."
"beautiful mountain."
Legend says
that Zeus used to hide Typhon there...
a monster of 100 heads...
and that it's still trying to escape.
So. Typhon didn't fall in love
with Zeus in 365 days.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ Lady. tell me something
'Cause I need somebody ♪
♪ Treat me as your boo. treat
Little child ♪
♪ Lady. tell me something
'Cause I need somebody ♪
♪ Treat me as your boo. treat
Little child ♪
♪ Livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ Yes. I'm livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ Save me from this fucking dark room ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ Yes. I'm livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm livin' in the dark room ♪
♪ Save me from this fucking dark room ♪
Get out!
- Get out. or else I...
- Else what?
Or I guarantee you.
this is the last time you'll see it.
I've order it.
and I'm gonna decide
when I'm going to see it.
See it on yourself.
No. wait.
Please. I need help.
Can you help me?
Someone kidnapped me. and I need help.
Good morning. sir.
Are you lost. baby girl?
If you feel like running.
you should wear a different kind of shoes.
Sometimes. fighting is futile.
You have to accept the situation.
The faster. the better for you.
You can either make it hard
for both of us for the next year. or...
take part in an adventure
that fate has given you.
It wasn't fate;
it was you.
Sometimes. we have to make our own luck.
Is it true what you said earlier?
What do you mean?
That you won't touch me
without my permission.
I'm not the monster you think I am.
I want my cell phone and laptop. Now.
And something normal for dinner.
Pierogi.
♪ You made a monster ♪
♪ You made a ♪
- ♪ You made a monster ♪
- ♪ Stitch by stitch ♪
♪ You made a ♪
♪ You patch me up then tear me down ♪
- ♪ You made a monster ♪
- ♪ Stitch by stitch ♪
♪ You made a ♪
- ♪ You made a monster ♪
♪ Monster ♪
- You look...
- I'm starving.
As you wished...
pierogi.
Is it good?
My grandma makes them better.
But you don't have to kill him.
I will give him couple of lessons.
So. what do you actually do?
ANNA
WHY ARE YOU NOT REPLYING?
I'M NOT GIVING UP!
I do...
business.
Hmm.
Massimo. I'm serious.
You want me to accept
a year-long declaration.
I have rights to know
what's waiting for me.
You will know
exactly what you need to know.
I have few...
companies.
hotels. clubs. restaurants.
It's like a corporation.
and I'm the CEO.
The whole is a part of a bigger operation.
But the details are useless...
and dangerous.
I was chosen the head of this family
after my dad's death.
It was not what I wished for.
I had no choice.
Exactly like me.
I would never have come to Sicily.
You'll change your mind.
You just have to...
help me a little.
Help?
I'd like you...
to teach me...
how to be gentle...
for you.
♪ You ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I feel the weight upon my chest ♪
♪ Suffocating of my lies ♪
♪ How do I know it's life? ♪
♪ I get it every time you're near ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ You... ♪
Mom.
Yeah. everything is fine.
I have to tell you something. though.
I was offered a new job in Sicily.
It's the best hotel on the island.
I was given a yearly contract.
Come on. stop worrying. You'll see.
You'll come to visit
and fall in love with the place as I have.
We're leaving today.
We'll be guests
at a few offshore parties.
so take that under consideration
while packing your bag.
Do you want anything from me.
or you're just looking?
Why are you looking at it?
Do you wanna touch it?
♪ Say what you think ♪
♪ Oh. baby. I could lose my mind
Yeah ♪
♪ You know that I can lose my mind
♪ What do you want me to be? ♪
- ♪ Headlight. hold tight ♪
- ♪ No. no. no. no ♪
♪ Oh. baby
You know I've been thinking about it ♪
♪ You know that
I've been dreaming about it ♪
♪ You know the deal
Don't make any promises ♪
♪ Promises ♪
- ♪ Got me ♪
- ♪ Flyin' ♪
♪ High ♪
Baby girl...
when your entire life is based on
taking everything with force.
it's hard to react in a different way.
Especially if someone is taking away
a pleasure you really desire...
Don't provoke me.
Or what?
She's got quite a temper.
At least I won't get bored.
Good luck. Massimo.
Let's go.
You comfortable enough?
Just untie me.
you fucking wop. and I'll show you...
English. please.
You have to earn the pleasure.
Laura.
♪ Good things are boring
I get antsy inside ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ But I need the sounds of birds
So I can feel alive ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Something's changing
Something we can't see ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm from another world ♪
♪ This thing is darker
Than the deep blue sea ♪
♪ I don't think I can be your girl... ♪
The problem is.
after the elections...
the whole deal might blow up.
We just need to pay them more.
Did you find her? Did you?
And how is she?
Are you happy?
Like everything.
It's difficult.
It always is.
Are you talking about me?
I've just said to my cousin
that you're a marvelous. gentle woman.
- Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Can you stop it?
Mmm.
I'm bored.
- I'm dirty.
- Stop it.
Is she going to bathe
in the fountain?
- No. she isn't.
- Is she?
- No.
- Wanna bet?
No. she won't do it.
Couldn't you use the bathroom?
Fountain was closer.
Of course.
Fuck!
Which period is that?
Early Michelangelo or late Caravaggio?
It was a gift.
Yeah. sure.
Not that you're a megalomaniac.
The great Massimo.
the slayer of lions and tiny women.
Stop it.
Maybe I don't want to stop.
- Take it.
In your dreams.
Are you saying no?
You have people for everything.
So. let them to this.
Are you sure?
Open the door. I want to leave.
Let me out. Open the door.
- Open this fucking door.
- Shh...
- Sit on the bed.
Fuck!
I'll do anything I want with you.
I was hoping you would do that.
It's a telescopic tube.
Every time you move.
it widens more and more.
I'm gonna show you what you're missing.
You see. Laura...
at this moment.
you're immobilized enough...
that you can't resist me anymore.
At the same time...
I have access
to absolutely every bit of your body.
Please...
Are you asking me to begin?
I'm gonna fuck you so hard...
that they will hear you scream in Warsaw.
I'm begging you.
Dress up.
We need to be in one of my clubs
in two hours.
♪ Here she comes again ♪
♪ With worries she can't hide... ♪
Listen to me.
He's gonna kill you.
And then. he's gonna kill me.
Shall we?
♪ Who can keep her sane? ♪
♪ Give her peace of mind? ♪
Listen. Laura.
We won't be alone. okay?
Some people will join us.
and we will have to discuss
some matters with them.
"Some people. some matters."
You are going to play Mafia. aren't you?
Listen. Laura.
This is not a fucking joke. okay?
Just keep your head down.
Hi. gorgeous.
Okay. you wait here.
Just one minute.
What the hell are you wearing?
A couple thousand euro of yours.
Don't provoke me.
Why?
Are you afraid that I am too good at it?
My dress is so short.
and could get inside me
without taking it off.
You will be mine. I guarantee it.
Then I'll do anything I want.
anytime I want with you.
Keep on dreaming.
♪ You heard the beat
Got the world on a string ♪
♪ To live forever
You'll do anything ♪
♪ Hatch your eggs
Grab the diamond ring ♪
♪ This is our night
To do everything ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's the time of our lives ♪
♪ I like the way that your looking at me ♪
♪ I like the way it falls in between ♪
♪ Getting lost. get lost in me ♪
♪ Take a ride
And you'll start to believe ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ This is the time of our lives ♪
♪ Music. music. music. cigarette... ♪
♪ It's all over. yeah ♪
♪ It's the time of our lives ♪
Finally. a real whore.
I'm going to fuck you so hard.
you won't be able to sit.
Come here.
- Come here.
- Fuck!
Get out!
I told you a thousand times.
Enough!
Just do your fucking duty.
Are you aware who you have shot. Massimo?
Do you know what you've done?
I couldn't just
sit there and watch.
This means war.
A war between two powerful families.
Do you get that?
The only thing you can do
is to get rid of Laura.
Do that and ask Anna for forgiveness.
And get rid of this damn boat. too.
Hey! Watch your fucking mouth!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
I'm sorry. I didn't think...
Yeah. you didn't think.
What's going on? Did you kill him?
- It's none of your business.
- You killed him?
I shot his hands.
I wouldn't have had to do it
if you didn't dress like a whore
and put on your little show.
So. that's my fault
that your friend tried to rape me?
That's my fault?
Fuck off.
Enough.
- Laura.
- Fuck off!
- Fuck off! Leave me alone.
- Where you going?
- Stop it. Where are you going?
- No. Get off me.
Laura. where are you going?
Fuck you.
- Can you stop that?
- Fuck!
Stop it!
- Don't touch me! Fuck you!
- Stop it!
- What are you doing?
- Fuck!
Fuck!
Laura!
Laura. breathe! Breathe.
Hey. Hey.
Okay?
I'm so grateful
that you're alive.
But in the same time. I wanna kill you.
You saved me.
Thank God I was so close.
Why are you so disobedient?
I'm sorry.
You have to understand...
I won't do it anymore.
I can't lose you. I don't want to.
You have to rest.
You're wet.
Don't play with me.
♪ Did you really think ♪
♪ I'd just forgive and forget? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ After catching you with her ♪
♪ Your blood should run cold ♪
♪ So cold ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ You two-timing. cheap. lying wannabe ♪
♪ You're a fool ♪
♪ If you thought
That I'd just let this go ♪
♪ I see red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ A gun to your head ♪
♪ Head ♪
♪ To your head ♪
♪ Now all I see is red ♪
♪ Red. red ♪
♪ Did you really just say ♪
♪ She didn't mean anything? ♪
♪ I'll remember those words ♪
♪ When I come for your soul ♪
♪ Your soul ♪
- ♪ Know that you ♪
♪ You dug your own grave ♪
♪ Now lie in it ♪
♪ You're so cruel ♪
♪ But revenge is a dish best served cold ♪
♪ I see red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ A gun to your head ♪
♪ Head ♪
♪ To your head ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Executioner-style ♪
♪ And there won't be no trial ♪
♪ Don't you know
That you're better off dead? ♪
♪ All I see is red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Now all I see is ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ I...♪
♪ Oh. you're so done ♪
♪ You better sleep
With one eye open tonight ♪
♪ I see red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Oh. a gun to your head ♪
♪ Head ♪
♪ To your head ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Executioner-style ♪
♪ And there won't be no trial ♪
♪ Don't you know
That you're better off dead? ♪
♪ All I see is red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Now all I see is ♪
♪ Red ♪
Mmm.
I want more.
We slept only one hour.
Are you tired already?
No.
I just wonder if you aren't too tired
for an evening surprise.
- I'm afraid of your surprises.
You'll like it.
What is it?
We're going to a ball.
A ball?
With the nice. long dresses?
Uh-huh.
Are you fucking crazy?
I have nothing to wear!
- Fuck!
So...
do you mind if I ask you to dance with me?
Don Massimo. you're asking?
How surprising.
Bravo.
Beautiful dance.
Thank you.
So. you've found her?
Laura.
Anna.
The first and real love of Massimo.
What do you want?
I expected better.
Enough.
Shall I kill her?
I'll take
the most precious thing you have.
Like you did to me.
Well?
I'm waiting.
Anna...
is quite recent.
How recent?
I left her the day you landed in Sicily.
I never lied to her.
Your portraits have been hanging
in my house for years.
Nobody believed that I will ever find you.
And... she didn't believe at all.
What did she say?
It doesn't matter.
I want to know.
She said that...
she will kill you.
Laura...
I will never let anyone hurt you.
I'll take care of her.
I want to leave.
Now.
♪ I'm gonna light like fire ♪
♪ I'm coming down like rain ♪
♪ I'm gonna break down barriers ♪
♪ I'm gonna play through the pain ♪
♪ I'm gonna rise like a phoenix ♪
♪ I'm gonna fight through the flame ♪
♪ Devil won't drag me down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm done ♪
♪ I'm all done playing games ♪
♪ I'm gonna light like fire ♪
♪ I'm coming down like rain ♪
♪ I'm gonna break down barriers ♪
♪ I'm gonna play through the pain ♪
♪ I'm gonna rise like a phoenix ♪
♪ I'm gonna fight through the flame ♪
♪ Devil won't drag me down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm done ♪
♪ I'm all done playing games ♪
Domenico will take you
to the airport tomorrow.
Your flight is at 8:00.
What?
What flight?
To Poland.
What are you talking about?
You said
that you want to visit your family.
- Yes. but...
- There's an apartment waiting for you
in Warsaw.
I'll join you there soon.
I love you.
I mean. come on.
Forget about Anna.
She's the past.
Is she?
Yes.
And you. my darling.
you are the fucking future.
Where exactly is she?
Well... Sorry.
Hello?
Stop.
What's going on?
Domenico. what happened?
Wait in Warsaw.
What?
Domenico?
♪ Braced cords as you turn ♪
♪ To this course you set upon ♪
♪ The sea coming all alive ♪
♪ And every ray when it arrives ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you won't be ♪
♪ Coming back ♪
Laura. no fucking way!
I wasn't talking to you.
I'll call you back.
I am going to kill you!
I thought you were kidnapped!
Just tell me one thing. okay?
What happened in fucking Sicily?
- Martin. I had enough of him.
- Did he piss you off?
I fell in love.
What the fuck?
Jesus. I know it sounds ridiculous.
I didn't want it. but things happened.
Fucking great.
Don't make me force it out of you.
Tell me. who is it?
He is... special.
What do you mean? He's got special needs?
Is he sick?
I know. he has flat feet.
Olga. shut up!
Tell me!
Imagine a strong alpha male.
who always knows what he wants.
He is your caretaker and your defender.
When you are with him.
you feel like a little girl.
He makes
all your sexual fantasies come true.
Um...
What's more.
he is one meter. 90 centimeters tall.
has absolutely no body fat.
and has been molded by God himself.
Did God mold his dick. too?
The devil did.
Fuck me.
So. what about him?
Mmm.
- We have to think this through.
- Mm-hmm.
He comes from a rich.
traditional Sicilian family.
They don't take foreigners for wives.
Right. now spare me the bullshit.
Tell me the truth.
Olga. I'm fucked up.
I was kidnapped by a gangster.
and then I fell in love with him.
And the worst thing
is that they keep me in the dark.
They treat me like some kind of doll.
They sent me to Poland.
and I still don't know a single thing.
That's why you need to fucking back out.
Do you understand?
Fuck all the Massimos. Martins.
and all the other mozzarellas.
It's time for a change.
A change of undies.
- We are going out.
- What?
What are you doing?
I'm conditioning my neighbors.
Hi. bitches!
Darius. just fucking look at you!
Please. don't leave. though.
Can you tell me why you woke me up
in the middle of the night? It's 1:00 p.m.
Fucking rejuvenation time!
Just look at her!
- Yeah. bad.
- Mmm.
How about some glasses?
Greg. I want some volume here.
Hello?
What? Did you suddenly have a stroke?
I was offered the position
of general manager at Preston.
You will be fucking General Preston!
Fucking shit!
Great. Mozzarella turned her brain
into pesto.
Now. that is some serious volume.
You're right. I'm not going
to just lie down and smell nice.
I'd like to lie down and smell nice...
Hey.
Hey! Stand in line!
There is a line to your ass.
♪ Don't call me up
I'm going out tonight ♪
♪ Feeling good now you're outta my life ♪
♪ Don't wanna talk about us ♪
♪ Gotta leave it behind
One drink and you're outta my mind ♪
♪ Now. now. take it up ♪
♪ Baby. I'm on a high
You're alone. going out of your mind  ♪
- Did you hurt yourself?
♪ And I don't wanna talk ♪
When falling down from heaven?
- Bye.
- ♪ 'Cause I'm here looking fine. babe ♪
♪ And I got eyes looking my way ♪
♪ And everybody's on my vibe. babe ♪
♪ Now. now. now. now
Don't call me up... ♪
It's for you. From that gentleman.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh-uh.
- Uh-uh.
- Mm-hmm.
- No.
Laura.
Hi.
Where were you all this time?
Can we talk?
I have nothing to say to you.
Laura. please. At least let me explain.
and then I'll leave.
Explain how your dick ended up
in a different girl's ass?
The moment you ran off from that pool...
I thought this through. You were right.
I ran after you. but you weren't there.
I started looking for you.
It got dark. so I went back to the hotel.
I found your letter. read it...
and lost my mind.
I decided I needed to get fucked up.
I called Michał...
And please. believe me...
that fucking first drink
was the last thing that I remember
from that evening.
When I woke up...
It doesn't change a thing
if you remember or not.
You slept with another girl.
But...
There are no "buts." Martin!
We belong to two different worlds.
There is no room for a woman in your life.
And I am not going to be your toy.
Do you understand?
It's all true. Laura.
But that is in the past.
I came to realize that...
I really love you.
I think I'm gonna puke.
I'm going home.
- Just five minutes.
- Goodbye!
Laura. I really miss you.
- But I don't miss you.
- So. it was all fake?
There was nothing between us?
It wasn't fake.
but it wasn't a healthy relationship.
- Honey. let's talk.
- We have nothing to talk about!
- Don't you get it? Nothing!
- We do.
No! You have already told me
what you had to say.
No. leave me alone!
- Bye!
- Wait!
I don't understand
what you two are saying.
but it's rather clear
that she wants you to leave.
Do I have to say it so you'll understand?
Martin. Massimo.
Meet each other.
But I think you've already met Martin.
Martin. come in!
Come in. please!
You are drunk.
We'll keep in touch.
Where have you been?
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
You look stunning. baby girl.
"You look stunning. baby girl."
You're a fucking egoist.
How could you?
How could you? You fuck!
♪ Closed eyes never feel safe ♪
♪ I'm tongue-tied ♪
♪ Never let out my rage ♪
♪ Try to break in this cage
But where would I go? ♪
♪ I'm stuck ♪
♪ Living a life of bad luck ♪
♪ Giving me nothing
Doors shut ♪
♪ Alone in my head
I'm out of control ♪
♪ Am I losing my sanity? ♪
♪ I'm over my head
I'm in a dark dream ♪
♪ I'm a prisoner here
They'll never let me leave ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Losing grip on reality ♪
♪ I'm over the edge
I yell and I scream ♪
♪ I'm a prisoner here
Come get me ♪
♪ Set me free ♪
♪ Hurt me. do what you want ♪
♪ I'm thirsty ♪
♪ Feeding me bones ♪
♪ Hunger is all that I know
I'm starving for air ♪
♪ Trapped here
Sinking in deeper ♪
♪ Cold sweat
Wet from a fever ♪
♪ I'm kept locked in a box
And nobody cares ♪
♪ Am I losing my sanity? ♪
♪ I'm over my head
I'm in a dark dream ♪
♪ I'm a prisoner here
They'll never let me leave ♪
♪ Losing grip on reality ♪
♪ I'm over the edge
I yell and I scream ♪
♪ I'm a prisoner here
Come get me ♪
♪ Set me free ♪
♪ Dark dreams
Every time I close my eyes ♪
♪ Demons coming after me
I'm tired ♪
♪ Please. every time I close my eyes
I see them coming after me. these... ♪
What's this?
Nothing.
I solved it.
What's going on?
I don't need 365 days.
Because?
'Cause I love you.
Say it again.
I love you.
♪ Am I losing my sanity? ♪
♪ I'm over my head
I'm in a dark dream ♪
♪ Let me leave ♪
Will you marry me?
- Fuck.
Does it mean "yes"?
Yes.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Almost the weekend ♪
♪ Putting in these hours every day ♪
♪ I'ma get what I'm seeking ♪
♪ Beeline to the top. I'm on my way ♪
♪ You should've figured it out by now ♪
♪ Here for the long run
Won't back down ♪
♪ I'm doing me ♪
♪ You're gonna see ♪
♪ Know your role
'Cause I know mine ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ If you're sleeping on me
I wouldn't advise ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Blazed my path a long. long time ago ♪
♪ Making really big moves
Sending haters right out the door ♪
♪ All this magic in the air
Got me on another wave ♪
♪ Keep up with me if you dare
Get this money. set the pace ♪
♪ I'm on a roll
Already know ♪
♪ Which way to go ♪
- ♪ All this magic in the air ♪
- No.
♪ Got me on another wave ♪
♪ Hate it or love it ♪
- Wanna bet?
- ♪ Secured my place. I'm here to stay ♪
♪ Climbing like it's nothing ♪
♪ I came for it all. no time to play ♪
♪ All this magic in the air ♪
♪ Got me on another wave ♪
♪ Keep up with me if you dare
Get this money. set the pace ♪
-
- ♪ Already know which way to go ♪
♪ All this magic in the air
Got me on another wave ♪
Calm down.
Everything will be fine.
I'm calm.
But do me a favor. and don't tell them
exactly what you do.
What do you want me to say?
I don't know.
Improvise.
Laura!
You look great as a blonde!
You look so pale. though.
Are you all right?
Mom...
Klara Biel.
Massimo. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Tomasz Biel.
- My pleasure. Massimo.
Who is he?
And what does he do?
My mom is asking
what do you do for a living.
I'm a gangster.
Really?
You will be the first in our family.
So. what are your intentions
with our daughter?
Only the evil ones.
We have to talk seriously.
- You like vodka?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
- Tomek!
Don't be so rude.
Well!
♪ Here comes the thunder ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder. oh ♪
♪ We gon' bring the rain ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder. oh ♪
♪ I ain't playing games ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder. oh ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder ♪
♪ I ain't playing games ♪
♪ Here comes the thunder. oh ♪
Good morning.
Sorry we didn't wait for you.
but I have to travel to Palermo.
It's okay. I'm not hungry yet.
I don't feel well.
- What's going on?
- Well. nothing. really.
Domenico will take you to the doctor.
Honey...
you said that...
nobody from Poland can come
to our wedding.
Even my parents.
You said it yourself that
you don't want them to know what I do.
Yes.
But I would love to have my best friend
to be next to me.
Olga knows everything about you.
I need her.
All right.
She'll be your bridesmaid.
I have to go now.
- Ciao. Mario.
- Come back soon.
I think you don't like me. Mario.
It's not true.
Stop it. I'm not blind.
It's nothing personal.
I don't like this situation.
You know...
that you have caused some commotion...
in our family.
I will arrange...
your friend's arrival.
Uh...
I just hope...
she's calmer than you are.
Olga!
Ciao!
What a ride! Fuck me!
I can't believe it!
Are you fucking out of your mind?
You have known each other for two months!
Stop it. Give me one.
You are pregnant.
I'll smoke two for your sake.
Fuck!
I don't get it. He forced you. right?
I'll tear him apart when I see him!
Olga. he doesn't know I'm pregnant!
He doesn't. And when he proposed.
I said yes willingly.
Laura. you are trapped in a cage!
Don't you see it? It's a golden cage.
but you are still a fucking prisoner!
Do you know what you are up against?
Olga. stop it!
What are you talking about? A cage?
- What am I supposed to do?
- I don't know.
Stop yelling. Do you take me for a fool?
You think I didn't know what I was doing?
Come here.
I love you. do you hear me?
I will always be there for you.
We will raise the child together.
It will be a beautiful child
with beautiful parents.
Not smart. though. but still.
Hey. girls!
Come on. I'm waiting here!
We're coming. sir!
- ♪ Come on. come on. come on ♪
- ♪ Oh. nah. nah ♪
♪ Come on. come on. come on ♪
♪ Oh. son. you better run
Before she come around ♪
♪ Her sweet talk will lock you down
Knock you down like... ♪
- ♪ Come on. come on. come on ♪
- ♪ Oh. nah. nah ♪
♪ Come on. come on. come on ♪
♪ Oh. son. you better run
Before she come around ♪
♪ Her sweet talk will lock you down
Knock you down like... ♪
♪ Ooh. baby. come a little closer
♪ I won't bite
I wanna get to know ya ♪
♪ Something I can't deny ♪
♪ I'm lost in your eyes ♪
♪ Ooh. baby. got my heart racing ♪
♪ Don't make a move... ♪
How long do we have to wait?
How long can you pamper yourself?
♪ So why'd you still wanna go? ♪
♪ You wanna ride full speed
Down the road ♪
♪ Come on. come on. come on ♪
It's. uh...
- You know...
Fuck!
Yeah...
I want to be with him and keep the child.
I know.
Well. you could stay
for a while in Sicily.
Fast cars. motorboats. good food.
Horny Italians.
Well. I don't know.
A lot of horny Italians!
What do you think I am here for?
Hell yeah!
Okay. stop talking me up.
Just call him.
- But...
- Call him.
What's up?
They're about to kill Laura.
Are you sure?
Yes. I'm sure.
Marco... go.
Go. Marco! Go!
Hi. honey.
How long does it take
to try on a dress?
As long as it takes.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Oh. fuck!
Massimo...
Go!
Can we talk after dinner?
About what?
Did something happen?
- Where is Massimo?
- By the swimming pool.
Of. fuck.
Laura?
♪ I don't want to keep you waiting ♪
♪ That's why you blame it on me ♪
♪ You just give me your secrets ♪
♪ And I want it too ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause this one's on you ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ And it's only true ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna feel it ♪
♪ Feel it so strong ♪
♪ This is making me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say goodbye ♪
♪ I'm gonna feel it ♪
♪ Feel it so strong ♪
♪ This is trying to make me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say goodbye ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ This is making me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ This is trying to make me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say goodbye ♪
♪ Mmm. even if I wanna play this ♪
♪ That's what they expecting from me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I will never let you go now ♪
♪ This is about you ♪
♪ 'Cause this one's on you ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ And it's only true ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna feel it ♪
♪ Feel it so strong ♪
♪ This is making me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say goodbye ♪
♪ I'm gonna feel it ♪
♪ Feel it so strong ♪
♪ This is trying to make me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say goodbye ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ This is making me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ This is trying to make me alive ♪
♪ We don't even have to say ♪
♪ Did you really think ♪
♪ I'd just forgive and forget? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ After catching you with her ♪
♪ Your blood should run cold ♪
♪ So cold ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ You two-timing. cheap. lying wannabe ♪
♪ You're a fool ♪
♪ If you thought
That I'd just let this go ♪
♪ I see red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Gun to your head ♪
♪ Head ♪
♪ To your head ♪
♪ Executioner-style ♪
♪ And there won't be no trial ♪
♪ Don't you know
That you're better off dead? ♪
♪ All I see is red ♪
♪ Red ♪
♪ Oh. red ♪
♪ Now all I see is red ♪
♪ Red ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm